Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Records, 1857-2008; XVIII.
  - I Tracings 8000-8999 (Box 203, Folder 29)
    - Plan showing surface to be acquired for gob dump at Eureka No. 4 Mine, 1909; I-8361
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Eureka No. 4 -- Notes: Annie Shallenberger; Pore and Smith; Charles D. Hough -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Crop table for Hough and Ruth tracts at Eureka No. 4 Mine south of swamp, undated; I-8362
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Eureka No. 4 -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Crop table for Hough and Ruth tracts at Eureka No. 4 Mine north of swamp, undated; I-8363
    - Plan showing lot at Fidelity Mine to be sold to Anton Oberman, undated; I-8369
      Operator: Fidelity Coal -- Mine: Fidelity -- Notes: Pittsburgh Coal Co.; Lewis McCrory; John Spahr -- Location: West Pike Run Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing lot at Fidelity Mine to be sold to James W. Parkins, undated; I-8369
    - Plan showing tract of land to be conveyed to Pittsburgh Coal Co. by John Lutz, 1910; I-8370
      Notes: Robert Conway -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing property of Hays and Wible Coal, 1910; I-8384
      Operator: Hays and Wible Coal -- Notes: A. J. Ruth -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing tract of land to be conveyed to Pittsburgh Coal Co. by Miller heirs, 1910; I-8386
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: Gob pile; Steubenville Pike -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing crop coal mined under John Hershey Jr. tract, undated; I-8387
      Notes: Christian Hershey -- Location: Penn Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing crop coal mined under Frank Abramovic tract, undated; I-8388
      Notes: James Gilmore; J. A. Shaub -- Location: Wilkins Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing surface to be purchased from Levi Horning, 1908; I-8394
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: C. Linhart; August Lutz -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing property to be purchased from Mark Kelso situate at Jumbo No. 2 Mine shaft, 1910; I-8399
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Jumbo No. 2 -- Location: Mount Pleasant Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing W. J. Fryer coal tract, 1910; I-8402
      Notes: Fryer farm; John M. Kelso, et al.; Pittsburgh, Cleveland & Youghiogheny Railroad -- Location: Upper Saint Clair Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing property to be leased to the United States government for experimental station at Wallace Station of the Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, 1910; I-8406
      Notes: Robert McElheny; Eli McElheny; John Wallace; Samuel Glenn -- Location: South Park Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan of surface at Spiketown, 8th, 9th, 10th owned by Pittsburgh Coal Co. at Fair Haven Mine, undated; I-8411
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Fair Haven -- Notes: Margaret Giffen; John Burns -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan of C. F. Lorish property showing entry and rib of coal covered with agreement with Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1911; I-8423
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: L. Fritz; Peter Portman -- Location: Kennedy Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing blocks of coal and drain entry to be conveyed by Pittsburgh Coal Co. to James Fox, 1911; I-8425
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: Jeremy Carter; Chess heirs; Fox Coal -- Location: Greentree (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing lot for proposed Lutheran church at Federal No. 2 Mine, 1911; I-8432
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Federal No. 2 -- Notes: Thom's Run -- Location: South Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing coal being worked by J. A. Hadden at National Mine, 1911; I-8445
      Operator: National Coal -- Mine: National -- Location: Rostraver Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan of land granted for the purpose of dumping material upon that is taken from shaft of Mrs. Malinda Brady's farm, 1912; I-8462
      Notes: Sam Swank -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing property and contours at Oak Mine, 1912; I-8473
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Oak; Enterprise -- Notes: C.S. Fetterman; Eliza McDonough; Knowlson; McNeely; Dr. Lincoln Oldshue; David Hunter -- Location: Wilkins Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing surface tract to be leased from Lucy Stahl, 1913; I-8487
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Eureka No. 4 -- Notes: William Hough; Josiah B. Pore; airway of mine -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing coal mined beyond crop line by Pittsburgh Coal Co. on Joseph H. Morrow property, 1913; I-8488
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: Mrs. Morrow heirs; Morrow Wilson heirs -- Location: Penn Township (Allegheny County).
    - Structural map of the Redstone Coal District, I-8489
      Notes: Pittsburgh Coal Co.; Pennsylvania Railroad; Smock Mine; Colonial Mine; Grindstone Shaft: Monongahela River -- Location: Franklin Township (Fayette County).
    - Index map showing principle lines of transportation in portions of Ohio, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia, 1904; I-8490
      Location: Ohio, Western Pennsylvania and West Virginia.
    - Plan showing surface at Mansfield Mine conveyed by John S. McCullough, et al. to Mansfield Coal & Coke Co., undated; I-8494
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Mansfield -- Notes: Col. James B. Glenn; Chartiers Valley Railroad; Wheeler H. Phelps -- Location: Scott Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing lot in Duquesne lot plan (revised), 1913; I-8497
      Operator: New York & Cleveland Gas Coal -- Mine: Duquesne -- Location: Wilkins Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing Federal Supply Co.'s store lot at Partridge Mine, 1928; I-8509
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Partridge -- Notes: S. J. Russell; Michael Burin; J. J. Crawford -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing trespass made by Daudet brothers on the Richard Donaldson tract of Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1929; I-8517
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Location: Robinson Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing surface property to be conveyed to the Boston Gas Coal Co. at Yough No. 2 Mine, 1929; I-8526
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Yough No. 2 -- Notes: Matthew Henderson; McCracken -- Location: Elizabeth Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing coal property to be leased to United States Coal & Supply Co. situate in the 19th Ward of Pittsburgh, 1929; I-8573
      Notes: R. Knowlson; David Hunter; J. Hughey; W. Hugey; J. W. House -- Location: Pittsburgh (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing coal to be conveyed to the Pennsylvania Railroad at Delmont No. 2 Mine, 1931; I-8634
      Operator: Delmont Gas Coal -- Mine: Delmont No. 2 -- Notes: J. W. Riddle tract; Michael Ringer; Pittsburgh Coal Co. -- Location: Franklin Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing coal to be leased to H. Fishwick, Jr. and J. Bauer at Montour No. 8 Mine, 1932; I-8667
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 8 -- Notes: Josephine Willock -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing proposed Cardox Charging Plant on property of Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1936; I-8741
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Notes: McNeilly Road -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing trespasses by Robert Ewing and Howard Davis at Partridge Mine, 1932; I-8669
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Partridge -- Notes: James Robinson tract; Samuel P. Davis surface; Jacob Johnston tract; Archie Marshall -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing surface to be leased from William Windsheimer, et ux. at the Margerum section of Dickson Mine, 1932; I-8676
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Dickson -- Notes: C. H. Lutz -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Location of proposed fan and fan house at United States Coal & Supply Co. Mine in the 19th Ward of Pittsburgh, 1933; I-8693
      Operator: United States Coal & Supply -- Notes: West Liberty Ave.; Wenzell Ave.; Brookline Blvd.; Sun Oil Co.; Harley Construction Products Co.; Pittsburgh Railways Co. right-of-way -- Location: Pittsburgh (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing surface to be leased at Cincinnati Mine from West Fry heirs, 1934; I-8700
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Cincinnati -- Notes: Pittsburgh & Charleroi Electric Railroad -- Location: Union Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing coal to be leased to Hugh Fishwick, Jr. at Montour No. 8 Mine, 1934; I-8701
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 8 -- Notes: David A. Cowan; Samuel Wallace; Josephine Willock -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing exchange of surface properties between Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Alex Scott Dunbar heirs in the Meloney section of Montour No. 9 Mine, 1934; I-8702
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 9 -- Notes: Mevay heirs; William Henry Wilson -- Location: North Fayette Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing trespasses of Osborne Mine, Youghiogheny & Ohio Coal Co. and Eureka Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1934; I-8707
      Operators: Youghiogheny & Ohio Coal; Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Osborne; Eureka -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing coal to be leased to Hugh Fishwick, Jr. at Montour No. 8 Mine, 1934; I-8713
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 8 -- Notes: David A. Cowan -- Location: Baldwin Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing proposed location of highway bridge over entry at Moon Run Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1936; I-8744
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Moon Run -- Notes: Red Dog Road; Mark Andrews; George R. Edmundson tract -- Location: Robinson Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing typical room necks for mechanical loading at Lindley Mine, 1936; I-8748
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Lindley -- Location: South Strabane Township (Washington County).
    - Plan and profile of proposed water tank and water line in the main hoist shaft at Montour No. 4 Mine, 1936; I-8754
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 4 --Location: Cecil Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing coal properties to be conveyed to Chartiers Gas Coal Co., 1936; I-8760
      Operator: Chartiers Gas Coal -- Notes: Nancy J. Hess; John Conner heirs; D. R. Bebout; James Tannehill; David M. Boyce -- Location: Cecil Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Arnold Mine of Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8791
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Arnold -- Location: Washington Township (Fayette County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Banning No. 1 Mine of Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8792
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Banning No. 1 -- Notes: Monongahela River -- Location: Perry Township (Fayette County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Banning No. 1 Mine of Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8793
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Banning No. 1 -- Notes: Cedar Creek -- Location: Rostraver Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Banning No. 2 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8794
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Banning No. 2 -- Location: Perry Township (Fayette County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Crescent No. 1 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8795
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Crescent No. 1 -- Location: West Pike Run Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Crescent No. 1 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8796
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Crescent No. 2 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8797
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Crescent No. 2 -- Notes: Monongahela River -- Location: Fallowfield Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Crescent No. 2 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8798
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Crescent No. 2 -- Location: Fallowfield Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Euclid Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8799
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Euclid -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Eureka Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8800
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Eureka -- Location: South Huntingdon Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Lindley Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8801
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Lindley -- Notes: Red Dog Road -- Location: North Strabane Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Lindley Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8802
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Lindley -- Location: North Strabane Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Midland Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8803
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Midland -- Location: Chartiers Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Montour No. 4 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8804
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 4 -- Location: Cecil Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Montour No. 9 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8805
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 9 -- Location: Robinson Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Montour No. 9 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8806
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Montour No. 10 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8807
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Montour No. 10 Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8808
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Moon Run Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8809
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Ocean Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8810
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Ocean -- Location: Elizabeth Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Ocean Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8811
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Ocean -- Location: Rostraver Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Somers Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8812
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Somers -- Location: Rostraver Township (Westmoreland County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Warden Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8813
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Warden Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., I-8814
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Warden -- Location: Forward Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Westland Mine of the Pittsburgh Coal Co., 1937; I-8815
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Westland -- Location: Chartiers Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing location of magazine at Solar Mine of the Solar Coal Co., 1937; I-8816
      Operator: Solar Coal -- Mine: Solar -- Location: Findlay Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing location of magazines at Alice Mine of the Solar Fuel Co., 1937; I-8817
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Alice -- Location: Jefferson Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing James Peters country pit at Venture Mine, undated; I-8846
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Venture -- Notes: Caroline Bloomer tract; workings -- Location: Greentree (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing lot to be conveyed to the Federal Supply Co. at Montour No. 10 Mine, 1939; I-8857
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 10 -- Notes: Piney Fork Creek; Route 88; O. C. Simmons; Potter heirs; E. B. Kraft -- Location: South Park Township (Allegheny County).
    - Exhibit A: plan showing proposed crossing of motor road over the Midway & Oakdale branch of the Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Railroad at Montour No. 9 Mine, 1940; I-8862
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 9 -- Notes: Dickson heirs; R. M. Donaldson -- Location: Robinson Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing standard panel of Chicago, Wilmington & Franklin Coal Co.'s Orient No. 1 Mine, undated; I-8867
      Operator: Chicago, Wilmington & Franklin Coal -- Mine: Orient No. 1 -- Location: Orient (Franklin County, Ill.).
    - Exhibit A: Plan showing proposed crossing of aerial tramway and tipple extension of public road (Route 62014) at Montour No. 4 Mine, 1941; I-8881
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Montour No. 4 -- Notes: Montour Railroad; Brush Run -- Location: Peters Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing air shaft lot at Westland Mine to be purchased from Nick Kozares, et ux., 1941; I-8885
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Westland -- Notes: H. O. McKnight; Thomas M. Paxton tract; Joseph T. Ryburn tract -- Location: Chartiers Township (Washington County).
    - Plan of Ontario Mine (blueprint), 1927; I-8916
      Operator: Ontario Gas Coal -- Mine: Ontario -- Notes: Bethlehem Mines Corporation; Vesta Coal Co. -- Location: North Bethlehem Township (Washington County).
    - Plan of Ontario Mine (reduced reproduction), 1927; I-8916
    - Plan showing store lot at Henderson Mine to be conveyed by Pittsburgh Coal Co. to Federal Supply Co., 1943; I-8986
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Henderson -- Notes: Montour Railroad; McPherson store lot tract; Nettie McPherson Tract -- Location: Cecil Township (Washington County).
    - Plan showing store lot at Crescent No. 1 Mine to be conveyed by Pittsburgh Coal Co. to Federal Supply Co., 1943; I-8987
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Crescent No. 1 -- Notes: Anderson Jeffries tract; Sarah Paxton; Levitske -- Location: West Pike Run Township (Washington County).
  - I Tracings 9000-9999 (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - Plan of trespass by M. R. Clements at Plum Creek Mine, 1944; I-9040
      Operator: New York & Cleveland Gas Coal -- Mine: Plum Creek -- Notes: A. B. Coleman; Thomas King heirs; Samuel Elliott -- Location: Plum Township (Allegheny County).
    - Plan showing proposed lease to Salvatore Gallo at Ramsey Mine, 1945; I-9056
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Ramsey -- Notes: R. Smith; J. Hill; J. Faithful; P. Thompson; E. Thompson; Pittsburgh Coal Co. surface -- Location: Mount Pleasant Township (Jefferson County, Ohio).
    - Plan showing proposed lease to William Piccolomini at Arnold Mine, 1945; I-9074
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Arnold -- Notes: Pittsburgh, McKeesport & Youghiogheny Railroad; James Hamer; Louis Kendall; Mansfield Cemetery; William Kendall; Woodvale Cemetery; Wilson McCrory -- Location: Washington Township (Fayette County).
    - Survey map of the property of A. W. and A. E. Marshall, undated; I-9152
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Location: Middleton Township (Columbiana County, Ohio).
    - Survey map of the property of John C. Miller, undated; I-9153
    - Survey map of the property of James W. Makall, undated; I-91545
    - Survey map of the Hannah F. Wilson tract, undated; I-9155
    - Plan of property to be conveyed to Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroads, sec. 36, 1946; I-9158
    - Plan showing expansion over a series of years, undated; I-9170
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Shaw -- Notes: Fit to H-5073 -- Location: Robinson Township (Washington County).
    - Engineering Department Records chart: List of mines operated by Pittsburgh Coal Co., undated; I-9218
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Lindley; Montour No. 4; Montour No. 9; Westland; Mathies; Montour No. 10; Crescent No. 1; Mongah; Ocean; Somers; Warden -- Notes: Intended to show amount of coal removed from each mine.
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 1 of 7), 1899-1940; I-9220
      Chart listing survey dates and their corresponding colors
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 2 of 7), 1941-1962; I-9220
      Chart listing survey dates and their corresponding colors.
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 3 of 7), 1899-1931; I-9220
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 4 of 7), 1931-1967; I-9220
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 5 of 7), 1931-1967; I-9220
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 6 of 7), 1967-1973; I-9220
    - Survey Dates and Colors (sheet 7 of 7), 1967-1982; I-9220
    - Plan showing trespass on the B. C. Jackman tract at Crescent No. 1 Mine, 1951; I-9228
      Operator: Pittsburgh Coal -- Mine: Crescent No. 1 -- Notes: Boundary line -- Location: West Pike Run Township (Washington County).
    - Library Rack Prints, undated; I-9237
      Chart of library rack prints: to be posted in the library office, referred to constantly, and will show how nearly up to date are the prints in the library rack for all mines.
    - Plan showing buildings at Crescent No. 1 Mine's third hill, 1954; I-9377
    - Joint Coal & Gas Committee's gas well pillars study, showing examples of pillar plans for various depths of cover, undated; I-9394
      Notes: Scale is 1 inch = 200 feet; No place to exceed 15' in width; Pillars to be a minimun of twice the width of the excavation driven.
    - The Underground Storage of Gas, 1952; I-9394
      Study entitled "The Underground Storage of Gas" by R. J. Murdy, chief geologist for the New York State Natural Gas Corporation, for presentation at the Mine Inspectors Institute of America, Sterling Hotel, Wilkes Barre, Pa., June 9-11, 1952.
    - Exhibit A: method of casing through a worked out coal seam, undated; I-9394
      Presented by the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Dept. of Mines and Mineral Industries, Oil and Gas Division.
    - Exhibit B: method of casing through two or more worked out coal seams, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit C: method of casing through one or more workable coal seams where coal has not been removed, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit D-1: use of packers to divert gas into inside casing, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit D-2: use of packers to divert gas into inside casing, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit E: plugging wells in an area not underlain by workable coal, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit F: plugging wells in an area underlain by workable coal, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit G-1: plugging of wells using a combination of cement and sand pumpings, undated; I-9394
    - Exhibit G-2: plugging of wells using only sand pumpings, mud or other equally non-porous material as approved by the Division, undated; I-9394
    - Letter from W. Roy Cunningham to well operators and coal mine operators in Southwestern Pennsylvania, April 29, 1957; I-9394
      Letter relates to a study of well failures by the Pennsylvania Dept. of Mines and Mineral Industries.
  - Accident reports (Box 203, Folder 31)
  - Mine maps, A-Z (Box 203, Folder 32)
  - Company sheets, A-Z (Box 203, Folder 33)
  - Property maps, A-Z (Box 203, Folder 34)
  - Pennsylvania maps (Box 203, Folder 35)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company technical drawings (Box 203, Folder 36)
  - Shannopin Coal Company technical drawings (Box 203, Folder 37)
  - Union Collieries technical drawings (Box 203, Folder 38)
  - Assorted technical drawings, tables, etc. (Box 203, Folder 39-40)
  - Appraisal of J. V. Thompson coal lands in Pennsylvania and West Virginia, May 1919 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Diamond drilling cost factors, 1921 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company, southwestern Pennsylvania, 1922 (Box 204, Folder 3)